Finding Aid for the Collection of Underground, Alternative and Extremist Literature LSC.0050
UCLA Library Special Collections
Underground, Alternative, and Extremist Literature collection
1900-1990
UCLA Library Special Collections
LSC.0050
95.5 Linear Feet (191 boxes, 1 oversize box)
Conditions Governing Access
Open for research. All requests to access special collections materials must be made in advance using the request button located on this page.
UCLA Catalog Record ID
UCLA Catalog Record ID: 9942328923606533
Scope and Content
Collection consists of newspapers and other materials representing American and some British and French underground, alternative and extremist literature. Includes materials from both sides of the political spectrum, such as Black Panther Party, Christian Anti-Communism Crusade, Communist Party, Industrial Workers of the World, and United Farm Workers Organizing Committee.
Organization and Arrangement
Arranged in the following series:
Underground newspapers arranged alphabetically (Boxes 1-17).
Organization materials arranged alphabetically (Boxes 18-192).
Related Material
Extremist Book Collection (Collection 552). Available at the UCLA Library Special Collections.
A Collection of Pamphlets of Extremist Movements (Collection 932). Available at the UCLA Library Special Collections.
Propaganda.; Underground publications.; Underground press publications -- United States -- Archives.
- Underground Newspapers
  - Action. New York, New York. (Box 1)
    General note
    Addenda to collection - January 1983.
  - Advocate. Los Angeles, California. (Box 1)
  - AFB. Champaign, Illinois. (Box 1)
    Addenda to collection - September 1978.
  - American Dream. Tempe, Arizona. (Box 1)
  - American Report, vol.1-3. Huntington, Indiana. (Box 15)
  - American Report, vol.3-4. Huntington, Indiana. (Box 16)
  - Appalachian. Boone, North Carolina. (Box 1)
  - Aquarian Agent. New York, New York. (Box 1)
  - Aquarius. Berkeley, California. (Box 1)
  - Artists Magazine. Albuquerque, New Mexico. (Box 12)
  - Artists' Workshop Press. Detroit, Michigan. (Box 1)
  - Astral Projection. Albuquerque, New Mexico. (Box 1, 12)
    Box 12 is Addenda to collection - September 1978.
  - Attack. Washington, D.C. (Box 1)
  - Aware. Los Angeles, California. (Box 1)
  - Berkeley Tribe. Berkeley, California. (Box 1)
  - Black Liberation News. Toronto, Canada. (Box 1)
  - California Independent. Fresno, California. (Box 1)
  - Canadian Tribune. Toronto, Canada. (Box 1)
  - Canyon Collective. Canyon, California. (Box 1)
  - Challenge. New York. (Box 1)
  - Chicago Journalism Review. Chicago, Illinois. (Box 1)
  - Chicago Seed. Chicago, Illinois. (Box 1)
  - Chicano Student Movement. Los Angeles, California. (Box 1)
  - Choice 68 Militant. New York, New York. (Box 1)
  - Common Sense. Union, New Jersey. (Box 1)
  - Contempt. Los Angeles, California. (Box 1)
  - Contrast. Los Angeles, California. (Box 1)
  - Daily World. New York, New York. (Box 2)
  - Digest. Baton Rouge, Louisiana. (Box 2)
  - Dock of the Bay. San Francisco, California. (Box 2)
  - Egoist. Oakland, California. (Box 2)
  - El Grito del Norte. Espanola, New Mexico. (Box 2)
  - El Malcriado. Keene, California., 1974 (Box 193, Folder 14)
    Issue
    Vol. VII, no. 7(July 31, 1974); Vol. VII, no. 10(Oct. 18, 1974)
  - El Oraculo de Mexico. Mexico City, Mexico. (Box 13)
  - Elysium New Living. Los Angeles, California. (Box 2)
  - Equal Justice. New York, New York. (Box 2)
  - Extra. Providence, Rhode Island. (Box 2)
  - F.T.E.. Los Angeles, California. (Box 2)
  - Flash. Pasadena, California. (Box 2)
  - Free Statesman. St. Cloud, Minnesota. (Box 2)
  - Free Trade. Los Angeles, California. (Box 2)
  - Free Venice Beachhead. Venice, California. (Box 2)
  - Freedom for Workers' Control. London, England. (Box 2)
  - Freedom Press. Santa Barbara, California. (Box 2)
  - FTA. Louisville, Kentucky. (Box 2)
  - Fusion. Boston, Massachusetts. (Box 2)
  - Go. Los Angeles, California. (Box 3)
  - Grass Roots Forum. San Gabriel, California. (Box 3)
  - Green Power. Los Angeles, California. (Box 3)
  - Grok. Goleta, California. (Box 3)
  - Harambee. Los Angeles, California. (Box 3)
  - Harbinger. Middletown, California. (Box 3)
  - Hollywood Free Paper. Hollywood, California. (Box 3)
  - Independent. New York, New York. (Box 3)
  - Indianapolis Free Press. Indianapolis, Indiana. (Box 3)
  - Innerspace. New York, New York. (Box 3)
  - Inquisition. Chicago, Illinois. (Box 3)
  - Isla Vista Argo. Goleta, California. (Box 3)
  - IT. London, England. (Box 3)
  - Julian Review. Baldwin Park, California. (Box 3)
  - Kaleidoscope. Milwaukee, Wisconsin. (Box 3)
  - Keeper's Voice. San Francisco, California. (Box 3)
  - Kent Dragonfire. Kent State, Ohio. (Box 3)
  - Kerista Swinger. Silver Spring, Maryland. (Box 3)
  - KRLA Beat. Los Angeles, California. (Box 3)
  - L.A. Action. Los Angeles, California., November 1968; Vol.1 no. 3 (November 1968) (Box 193, Folder 7)
  - L.A. Digger News. North Hollywood, California., undated (Box 193, Folder 10)
    ca. 1960's
  - L.A. Student Mobilizer, August 1967 (Box 193, Folder 3)
    6 August 1967
  - La American. Albuquerque, New Mexico. (Box 13)
  - La Causa. Los Angeles, California., 22 May 1967 (Box 193, Folder 1)
    Vol.1 no. 6(22 Mayo 1967?)
  - La Guardia. Milwaukee, Wisconsin., October 1969 (Box 193, Folder 12)
    Vol. 1, no. 2 (October 1969)
  - Labor Action Independant Socialist Weekly. New York, New York., 15 October 1956 (Box 4, Folder 22)
    Oct. 4, 1954; Oct. 15, 1956
  - Las Vegas Free Press. Las Vegas, Nevada., 1970 (Box 193, Folder 21)
    Vol. 1, no. 6 (Feb.5, 1970); no. 9,(Feb. 26 - Mar.4, 1970); no. 29 (July 22, 1970)
  - Le Figaro Litterarie. Paris, France., February 1970 (Box 193, Folder 18)
    issue
    no. 1237, 2- 8 Fevrier 1970
  - Leviathan. San Francisco, California., 1970 (Box 193, Folder 2)
    Vol. 2, no. 4 (Fall 1970)
  - Lewis-McChord Free Press. Tacoma, Washington., February 1971; Vol.2 no. 2 (February 1971) (Box 193, Folder 5)
  - Liberated Guardian. New York. (Box 14)
  - Literary Times. Chicago, Illinois., 1966 (Box 193, Folder 13)
    vol. 4, no. 5 (Winter, 1966)
  - Little Paper. San Francisco, California., 1968 (Box 193, Folder 8)
    no. 25 (1986)
  - Long Beach Free Press. Long Beach, California., undated (Box 193, Folder 9)
    Vol. 1, no. 14 (Oct. 1-15)
  - Los Angeles Star. Los Angeles, California, 1971-1972 (Box 193, Folder 11)
    Issues
    Vol. 1, no. 1(July 1971); Vol. 1, no. 12 (May 5, 1972)
  - Marijuana Review. Rapid City, South Dakota., 1970; Vol. 1, no. 5 Jan.-Jun. 1970 (Box 193, Folder 4)
  - Match. Tucson, Arizona., January 1972 (Box 193, Folder 17)
    Vol. 3, no. 3 (January 1972)
  - Maverick. San Francisco, California., 1967 (Box 193, Folder 19)
    Vol. 1, no. 1 (1967)
  - Messiah's World Crusade. San Francisco, California., undated (Box 193, Folder 16)
  - Midlothian Mirror. Midlothian, Texas., 25 September 1969 (Box 193, Folder 23)
    Vol. 26, no. 43 (Sept. 25, 1969)
  - Morning Sun. Tempe, Arizona., 1967 (Box 193, Folder 15)
    Vol. 1, no. 4 (1967)
  - Muhammad Speaks. Chicago, Illinois., 6 April 1973 (Box 193, Folder 20)
    Vol. 12, no. 30 (April 6, 1973)
  - National Underground Review. New York, New York. (Box 6)
  - New York Element. New York, New York. (Box 7)
  - New York Free Press. New York, New York. (Box 7)
  - Nommo. Los Angeles, California. (Box 7)
  - Nuclear Oponents. Allendale, New Jersey. (Box 7)
  - Octopus Free Press. Ottawa, Canada. (Box 7)
  - Old Town Gazette. Albuquerque, New Mexico. (Box 14)
  - Open Cell. Berkeley, California. (Box 7)
  - Open City. Los Angeles, California. (Box 7)
  - Oracle. City of Los Angeles. Los Angeles, California, March 1967 (Box 193, Folder 6)
    Vol. 1 no. 1 (March 1967)
  - Organ. Berkeley, California. (Box 7)
  - Other Scenes. Los Angeles, California. (Box 7)
  - Outcry. Berkeley, California. (Box 7)
  - P.O. Frisco. San Francisco, California. (Box 8)
  - Pacific Sun. San Rafael, California. (Box 7)
  - Pack Rat. Berkeley, California. (Box 7)
  - Paper. East Lansing, Michigan. (Box 7)
  - Peace and Freedom National Organizer. Chicago, Illinois. (Box 8)
  - Peace and Justice. Hollywood, California. (Box 8)
  - Peoples' Free Press. Reseda, California. (Box 8)
  - Picket Line. Los Angeles, California. (Box 8)
  - Planet. Los Angeles, California. (Box 8)
  - Provo, the Underground Tab. Hollywood, California. (Box 8)
  - Radical Rag. Berkeley, California. (Box 8)
  - Rags. London, England. (Box 8)
  - Rat Subterranean News. New York, New York. (Box 8)
  - Rebirth. New York, New York. (Box 8)
  - Renaissance. Los Angeles, California. (Box 8)
  - Resist. Palo Alto, California. (Box 8)
  - Revolution. San Diego, California. (Box 8)
    in Collection 1000, Little Mag.
  - Revolutionary Youth Movement. Chicago, Illinois. (Box 8)
  - Rising Sign. Sherman Oaks, California. (Box 8)
  - Rising Up Angry. Chicago, Illinois. (Box 8)
  - Rock. New York, New York. (Box 8)
  - San Diego Door to Liberation. San Diego, California. (Box 9)
  - San Francisco Express Times. San Francisco, California. (Box 9)
  - San Francisco Free Press. San Francisco, California. (Box 9)
  - San Francisco Quarterly. San Francisco, California. (Box 9)
  - San Jose Red Eye. San Jose, California. (Box 9)
  - Schism. Mt. Vernon, Ohio. (Box 9)
  - Screw. New York, New York. (Box 9)
  - Second City. Chicago, Illinois. (Box 9)
  - Sermonette. New York, New York. (Box 9)
  - So. Calif. Oracle. Los Angeles, California. (Box 9)
  - South Hayward News. Hayward, California. (Box 14)
  - Star West. Sausalito, California. (Box 9)
  - Strategic Hamlet. Goleta, California. (Box 9)
  - Student Action. San Francisco, California. (Box 9)
  - Sunday Ramparts. San Francisco, California. (Box 9)
  - Swamp Erie Pipe Dream. Cleveland, Ohio. (Box 9)
  - Tempo. Los Angeles, California. (Box 10)
  - The American Mercury. Torrance, California. (Box 1)
  - The Pentagon Paper. Los Angeles, California. (Box 8)
  - The Rising. San Francisco, California. (Box 8)
  - The South End. Detroit, Michigan. (Box 17)
  - The Student Federalist. Washington, D.C. (Box 16)
  - The Tidings. Los Angeles, California. (Box 10)
  - This is Happening. Woodland Hills, California. (Box 10)
  - This Paper Belongs to the People. Toronto, Canada. (Box 10)
  - Thumb In It. Beverly Hills, California. (Box 10)
  - Times of Israel. Tel Aviv, Israel. (Box 10)
  - Tribal Messenger, vol.1-3. Albuquerque, New Mexico. (Box 13)
  - Tribal Messenger, vol.4-5. Albuquerque, New Mexico. (Box 14)
  - Tuesday's Child. Hollywood, California. (Box 10)
  - United Irishman. Dublin, Ireland. (Box 10)
  - Universal Life. Modesto, California. (Box 10)
  - Vanguard. San Francisco, California. (Box 10)
  - VDRSVP. San Francisco, California. (Box 10)
  - Vicksburg Citizens' Appeal. Vicksburg, Mississippi. (Box 17)
  - Village Press. Los Angeles, California. (Box 10)
  - Vision. Berkeley, California. (Box 10)
  - Vista. Los Angeles, California. (Box 10)
  - War Behind Walls. San Francisco, California. (Box 11)
  - Warren-Forest Sun. Detroit, Michigan. (Box 11)
  - Washington Free Press. Washington, D.C. (Box 11)
  - West Wind. Los Angeles, California. (Box 11)
  - When. Los Angeles, California. (Box 11)
  - Women's Liberation. Albany, California. (Box 11)
  - Workers Vanguard. New York, New York. (Box 11)
  - Workers World. New York, New York. (Box 11)
  - World Countdown. Los Angeles, California. (Box 11)
  - World of Soul, Jazz and Pop. New York, New York. (Box 11)
  - World Tribune. Santa Monica, California. (Box 11)
  - Worrier. Los Angeles, California. (Box 11)
  - Young People's Informer. n.p. (Box 11)
  - Young Socialist Challenge. New York, New York. (Box 11)
  - ZPG Newsletter. Palo Alto, California. (Box 11)
  - Zygote. Los Angeles, California. (Box 11)
- Organization Materials
  - A
    - ACOA, n.p. (Box 18)
    - Action Communication Center. Los Angeles, California. (Box 18)
    - Ad Hoc Committee for Easter-Passover Walk & Rally. Los Angeles, California. (Box 18)
    - Ad Hoc committee for intellectual freedom. Los Angeles, California. (Box 18)
    - Ad Hoc Student Committee for Constitution Liberties, n.p. (Box 18)
    - Ad Hoc Vietnam Peace Committee. Los Angeles, California. (Box 18)
    - Advertising Council, Incorporated. New York, New York. (Box 18)
    - Affiliated Schools for Workers, Incorporated. New York, New York. (Box 18)
    - Alamo Christian Church. Alma, Arkansas. (Box 18)
    - Alan Guttmacher Institute. New York, New York. (Box 18)
    - Alert Against Communism in California. Los Angeles, California. (Box 18)
    - Alert Americans Association. Los Angeles, California. (Box 18)
    - All City Employees Protective League. Los Angeles, California. (Box 18)
    - All London Tenants' Defense League. London, England. (Box 18)
    - All-American Conference to Combat Communism. Washington, D.C. (Box 18)
    - All-Union Central Council of Trade Unions, Moscow (Box 18)
    - Alliance for Survival. Los Angeles, California. (Box 18)
    - Allied Veterans for Preservation of American Principles, n.p. (Box 18)
    - Amandhla. Black Students Alliance Newsletter. Los Angeles, California. (Box 18)
    - Ambijan Committee for Emergency Aid to the Soviet Union, n.p. (Box 18)
    - Amerasia, n.p. (Box 18)
    - America First Committee. Chicago, Illinois. (Box 18)
    - America Speaks. Los Angeles, California. (Box 18)
    - America's Future, Incorporated, New Rochelle. New York, New York. (Box 26)
    - American - African Affairs Association, Incorporated. New York, New York. (Box 18)
    - American - Asian Educational Exchange. New York, New York. (Box 18)
    - American - Israeli Civil Liberties Coalition, Incorporated. New York, New York. (Box 21)
    - American Alliance for Labor and Democracy, n.p. (Box 18)
    - American Analyst. Hollywood, California. (Box 18)
    - American Association for Labor Legislation. Madison, Wisconsin. (Box 18)
    - American Association for the United Nations, Incorporated, n.p. (Box 18)
    - American Association of Scientific Workers, n.p. (Box 18)
    - American Association on Unemployment. New York, New York. (Box 18)
    - American Atheist. Austin, Texas. (Box 18)
    - American Birthright Committee. Los Angeles, California. (Box 18)
    - American Capsule News. Washington, D.C. (Box 18)
    - American Challenge. Birmingham, Alabama. (Box 19)
    - American Christian Freedom Society Incorporated. Los Angeles, California. (Box 19)
    - American Christian Palestine Committee. New York, New York. (Box 19)
    - American Circle. New York, New York. (Box 19)
    - American Classical College Press. Albuquerque, New Mexico. (Box 19)
    - American Coalition. Washington, D.C. (Box 19)
    - American Coalition of Patriotic Societies, Incorporated. Washington, D.C. (Box 19)
    - American Commentator. Denver, Colorado. (Box 19)
    - American Committee for Anti-Nazi Literature. New York, New York. (Box 20)
    - American Committee for Cultural Freedom, n.p. (Box 20)
    - American Committee for International Information. New York, New York. (Box 20)
    - American Committee for Justice to China. New York, New York. (Box 20)
    - American Committee for Non-participation in Japanese Aggression. New York, New York. (Box 20)
    - American Committee for Protection of Foreign Born. New York, New York. (Box 20)
    - American Conservative Union. Washington, D.C. (Box 20)
    - American Council for Judaism. New York, New York. (Box 20)
    - American Council Institute of Pacific Relations. New York, New York. (Box 20)
    - American Council of American - Soviet Friendship, Incorporated. New York, New York. (Box 21)
    - American Council of Christian Laymen. Madison, Wisconsin. (Box 21)
    - American Council on Soviet Relations, n.p. (Box 21)
    - American Documentary Films, Incorporated. San Francisco, California. (Box 21)
    - American Economic Foundation, n.p. (Box 21)
    - American Education Association. New York, New York. (Box 21)
    - American Education Press, Incorporated, n.p. (Box 21)
    - American Educational League. Los Angeles, California. (Box 21)
    - American Ethical Union. New York, New York. (Box 21)
    - American Eugenics Party. Los Angeles, California. (Box 21)
    - American Federation for Polish News. New York, New York. (Box 21)
    - American Fellowship Forum. New York, New York. (Box 21)
    - American Flag Committee. Philadelphia, Pennsylvania. (Box 21)
    - American Foundation, Incorporated. New York, New York. (Box 21)
    - American Freedom Association. Los Angeles, California. (Box 21)
    - American Friends of Democratic Sudentens (?). New York, New York. (Box 21)
    - American Friends of Polish Democracy. New York, New York. (Box 21)
    - American Friends of Spanish Democracy. New York, New York. (Box 21)
    - American Guardian. Oklahoma City, Oklahoma. (Box 21)
    - American Heritage Protective Committee. San Antonio, Texas. (Box 21)
    - American Honest Money Legion. Los Angeles, California. (Box 21)
    - American Humanist Association, n.p. (Box 192)
    - American Humanist Association. Washington, D.C. (Box 21)
    - American Independent Party, n.p. (Box 21)
    - American Indian Movement, n.p. (Box 21)
    - American Institute for Economic Research. Great Barrington, Massachusetts. (Box 21)
    - American Israel Public Affairs Committee. Washington, D.C. (Box 21)
    - American Jewish Committee. New York, New York. (Box 22)
    - American Jewish Congress, n.p. (Box 22)
    - American Jewish Labor Council, n.p. (Box 22)
    - American Labor Party, n.p. (Box 22)
    - American Labor Union Educational Society, n.p. (Box 22)
    - American League Against War and Fascism. New York, New York. (Box 22)
    - American League for Democratic Socialism. New York, New York. (Box 22)
    - American League for Peace and Democracy. New York, New York. (Box 22)
    - American Liberty League. Washington, D.C. (Box 22)
    - American Liberty News. Los Angeles, California. (Box 22)
    - American Life Lobby Incorporated. Stafford, Virginia. (Box 22)
    - American Mutuality Foundation - A.C.F.S. Incorporated. Los Angeles, California. (Box 22)
    - American Nationalist. Washington, D.C. (Box 22)
    - American Nationalist. St. Louis, Missouri. (Box 23)
    - American Nazi Party, n.p. (Box 23)
    - American Observer. Washington, D.C. (Box 23)
    - American Peace Mobilization. Los Angeles, California. (Box 23)
    - American People's Mobilization. New York, New York. (Box 23)
    - American Press. New York, New York. (Box 18)
    - American Progress Foundation. Los Angeles, California. (Box 23)
    - American Prophetic League, Incorporated. Los Angeles, California. (Box 23)
    - American Rangers. Beverly Hills, California. (Box 23)
    - American Referendum Association, Incorporated. New York, New York. (Box 23)
    - American Relations Society. Los Angeles, California. (Box 23)
    - American Russian Institute, Incorporated. New York, New York. (Box 23)
    - American Security Council. Chicago, Illinois. (Box 23)
    - American Security Council. Washington, D.C. (Box 24)
    - American Slav Congress. New York, New York. (Box 24)
    - American Society for Russian Relief, Incorporated. Hollywood, California. (Box 24)
    - American State. Los Angeles, California. (Box 24)
    - American States' Rights Party. Birmingham, Alabama. (Box 24)
    - American Streak Periodical. New York, New York. (Box 24)
    - American Student Union, n.p. (Box 24)
    - American Tariff League. New York, New York. (Box 24)
    - American Viewpoint, Incorporated. New York, New York. (Box 24)
    - American Vigilance Association. New York, New York. (Box 24)
    - American Vigilante. New York, New York. (Box 24)
    - American White Guard, n.p. (Box 24)
      See Anti-semitism.
    - American Women Against Communism. New York, New York. (Box 24)
    - American Worker - Consumer. Los Angeles, California. (Box 24)
    - American Youth Act, n.p. (Box 24)
    - American Youth Congress, n.p. (Box 24)
    - American Zionist Youth Commission. New York, New York. (Box 24)
    - Americanism Committee. Atlanta, Georgia. (Box 25)
    - Americanism Educational League. Los Angeles, California. (Box 25)
    - Americans (of Lebanese - Syrian Ancestry) for America. Downey, California. (Box 26)
    - Americans for Constitutional Action. Washington, D.C. (Box 25)
    - Americans for Democratic Action. Washington, D.C. (Box 26)
    - Americans for National Security. Washington, D.C. (Box 26)
    - Americans for Patriotism. Columbus, Georgia. (Box 26)
    - Americans for Religious Liberty. Silver Spring, Maryland. (Box 26)
    - Americans on Guard. Costa Mesa, California. (Box 26)
    - Americans United. Washington, D.C. (Box 26)
    - Americans United for World Government, Incorporated. New York, New York. (Box 26)
    - Americans United for World Organization, Incorporated. New York, New York. (Box 26)
    - Ammerican Committee for the Defense of Leon Trotsky. New York, New York. (Box 20)
    - Amnesty, n.p. (Box 27)
    - Amnesty International, n.p. (Box 28)
    - Anarchism and anarchists, n.p. (Box 29)
    - Angry Arts of Southern California. Los Angeles, California. (Box 29)
    - Angry Voice. Lawndate, California. (Box 29)
    - Anti-Communism Voters League. Los Angeles, California. (Box 30)
    - Anti-Communist. Oak Park, Illinois. (Box 30)
    - Anti-Communist Federation of America. Los Angeles, California. (Box 30)
    - Anti-Communist movements - U.S., n.p. (Box 31, Box 32)
    - Anti-Defamation League of B'Nai B'rith, n.p. (Box 30)
    - Anti-Fascist Literature Committee. New York, New York. (Box 30)
    - Anti-Imperialist. Brookline, Massachusetts. (Box 30)
    - Anti-Nazi movements, n.p. (Box 30, 33)
    - Anti-Nuclear Movements, n.p. (Box 33)
    - Anti-Profit Press. Seattle, Washington. (Box 30)
    - Anti-Semitism, n.p. (Box 34)
    - Anti-Smoking Movements, n.p. (Box 36)
    - Anticomintern., English edition, n.p. (Box 30)
    - Arab League Office. New York, New York. (Box 36)
    - Argus Publishing Company. Chicago, Illinois. (Box 36)
    - Aroused Christian Americans, Incorporated. San Diego, California. (Box 36)
    - Artist's Tower. Los Angeles, California. (Box 36)
    - Artists Call Against U.S. Intervention in Central America. San Francisco, California. (Box 36)
    - Arts Committee of the Coalition for Handgun Control. Los Angeles, California. (Box 36)
    - Arts, Sciences Professions Council of Progressive Citizens .... Hollywood, California. (Box 36)
    - Asian Labor Education Center. Diliman, Quexon City. (Box 36)
    - Assembly of Men & Women in the Arts Concerned with Vietnam, n.p. (Box 36)
    - Association for Friendship & Cultural Relations USA - USSR. Los Angeles, California. (Box 36)
    - Association for International Development. Patterson, New Jersey. (Box 36)
    - Association for Interpersonal Relations. Los Angeles, California. (Box 36)
    - Association of Citizens' Councils of Mississippi. Winona, Mississippi. (Box 36)
    - Association of Scientific Workers. London, England. (Box 36)
    - Association on American Indian Affairs, Incorporated. New York, New York. (Box 36)
    - Astral Projection. Albuquerque, New Mexico. (Box 1, 12)
      Box 12, Addenda to collection - September 1978.
    - Astrology, n.p. (Box 36)
    - Atomic weapons and disarmament, n.p. (Box 36)
    - Australian Labor Party, n.p. (Box 37)
    - Autarchy, n.p. (Box 37)
    - Awake America. Burbank, California. (Box 37)
  - B
    - Barrradas League. San Francisco, California. (Box 37)
    - Bay Area Spartacist Committee. Berkeley, California. (Box 37)
    - Ben Leider Memorial Fund. New York, New York. (Box 37)
    - Berkeley Anti-Criminal Syndicalism Committee. San Francisco, California. (Box 37)
    - Berrigan Committee. Los Angeles, California. (Box 37)
      SEE ALSO: Committee for Father Daniel Berrigan.